Guide to the Yale University Divinity School Memorabilia Collection
Yale University Divinity School Library
- YDS Publications and Lectures, 1822-present; Series IV
  - Lecture series, The material regarding Named Lecture Series is general in nature; text of the lectures is not available in this series, though may be available in published form or on audio recordings. The files contain correspondence between the Dean of YDS and the lecturers, including letters 
    - Nathaniel Taylor Lectures (34 folders), 1950/51-2003/04 (Box IV-19)
      2003-2004 David Kelsey (10/14-16/03) 2001-2002 Nicholas Wolterstorff (10/2-4/01) 1999-2000 David Tracy (10/12-14/00) 1997-1998 Jurgen Moltmann (10/14-15/97) 1995-1996 Gordon Kaufman (10/9-12/95) 1993-1994 Sallie McFague (2/8-10/94) 1989-1990 Jane Dempsey Douglass (2/13-15/90) 1987-1988 John B. Cobb, Jr. (2/8-11/88) 1983-1984 Dorothee Solie (2/84) 1981-1982 Julian Hartt (2/81) 1978-1979 Paul Riccoeur (2/79) 1976-1977 Wolfhart Pannenberg (2/77) 1974-1975 Albert C. Outler (2/18-20/75) 1970-1971 Thomas F. Torrance (4/20-22/71) 1968-1969 Richard M. Hare (12/10-12/68) 1962-1963 Wilfred Cantwell Smith (4/16-18/63) 1960-1961 Austin Farrer (4/4-6/61) 1959-1960 Gustave Weigel (4/19-21/59) 1958-1959 Wilhelm Pauck (3/31-4/2/59) 1957-1958 Visser't Hooft (9/23-26/57) 1974-1975 Albert C. Outler (2/18-20/75) 1970-1971 Thomas F. Torrance (4/20-22/71) 1968-1969 Richard M. Hare (12/10-12/68) 1962-1963 Wilfred Cantwell Smith (4/16-18/63) 1960-1961 Austin Farrer (4/4-6/61) 1959-1960 Gustave Weigel (4/19-21/59) 1958-1959 Wilhelm Pauck (3/31-4/2/59) 1957-1958 Visser't Hooft (9/23-26/57) 1954-1955 Roger Hazelton (4/12-14/55) 1952-1953 Daniel Williams (4/7-9/53) 1950-1951 Roland Bainton, Robert Calhoun, Luther Weigle, Sammuel Morison (4/3-5/51)
    - Templeton Lectures (4 folders), 1998, 1999, 2008 (Box IV-19)
      David Munteanu (4/22/08) Ian Barbour (10/13/99) David B. Larson (4/9/98) Letty Russell (Moderator) Panel Discussion (10/14/98)
    - Faculty and Miscellaneous Lectures (13 folders), 1984-2003 (Box IV-20)
      Amy Platinga Pauw (10/10/03) Jaroslav Pelikan (4/3/03) Demetrios Traketellis (4/29/03) Oswald Bayer (2/22/01) Oliver O'Donovan (9/25/98) Michael Perry-Utowjtz Lectureship (4/15/97) Jim Wallis (10/19/94) Peter Pokorny (10/22/92) James and Evelyn Whitehead (10/16/87) Robert A. K. Runcie (10/9/86) John Cobb (10/15/84) J. S. K. Ward (4/11/94) Stephen Herholdt (12/8/94)
- Audio-Visual Materials, Series V; *NOTE: CDs of Convocation lectures are available for purchase from the Yale Divinity School Bookstore (http://www.yaledivinitybookstore.com/category/audio-and-lectures)
  Series V, Audio-Visual Materials, contains photographs, audiotapes/CDs, and videotapes/DVDs documenting many aspects of Yale Divinity School life, including faculty, staff, alumni, students and events.
  Class composite photos & panoramic photographs of various classes are stored in drawers in the Map Chest.
  Audio tapes and compact discs are available for some faculty lectures and other special lectures including those given during the annual Convocation*.
  - Photographs
    - Faculty
      - Adams, Harry B (Box V-1)
      - Adams, Marilyn McCord (Box V-1)
      - Ahlstrom, Sydney (Box V-1)
      - Annand, James (Box V-1)
      - Archer, Clark (Box V-1)
      - Attridge, Harold (Box V-1)
      - Bacon, B.W. (Box V-1)
      - Bainton, Roland (Box V-1)
      - Baker, Robert (Box V-1)
      - Bartlett, David (Box V-1)
      - Baugh, W. (Box V-1)
      - Bigwood, Jill (Box V-1)
      - Bliss, William (Box V-1)
      - Bollier, John (Box V-1)
      - Brewster, Kingman Jr. (Box V-1)
      - Bond, Gilbert (Box V-1)
      - Brown, Charles Reynolds (Box V-1)
      - Brown, Thomas (Box V-1)
      - Calhoun, Robert Lowry (Box V-1)
      - Campbell, J.Y (Box V-1)
      - Carr, Aute (Box V-1)
      - Childs, Brevard (Box V-1)
      - Chiola, Richard (Box V-1)
      - Chopp, Rebecca (Box V-1)
      - Clark, Charles H. (Box V-1)
      - Coffin, William Sloane (Box V-1)
      - Connell, David (Box V-1)
      - Cook, John (Box V-1)
      - Couch, A. Edward (Box V-1)
      - Dahl, George and Elizabeth (Box V-1)
      - Dahl, Nils (Box V-1)
      - Davis, Jerome (Box V-1)
      - Day, Jeremiah (Box V-1)
      - Dinkler, Eric (Box V-1)
      - Dinsmore, Charles Allen (Box V-1)
      - Dittes, James (Box V-1)
      - Dobihal, E. (Box V-1)
      - Dwight, Timothy (Box V-1)
      - Ewing, Lucia (Box V-1)
      - Farley, Margaret (Box V-1)
      - Fern, Richard (Box V-1)
      - Fisher, George Park (Box V-1)
      - Fitch, Eleazar T. (Box V-1)
      - Forman, Charles (Box V-1)
      - Forsberg, Joan (Box V-1)
      - Franklin, R. W. (Box V-1)
      - Frei, Hans (Box V-1)
      - French, Richard (Box V-1)
      - Garrett, Susan (Box V-1)
      - Gibbs, Josiah W. (Box V-1)
      - Gill, Katherine J. (Box V-1)
      - Gomes, Peter (Box V-1)
      - Goodrich, Chauncey A. (Box V-1)
      - Greaves, William H. (Box V-1)
      - Greer, Rowan (Box V-1)
      - Gundry-Volf, Judy (Box V-1)
      - Gustafson, James M. (Box V-1)
      - Hall, Peter Dobkin (Box V-1)
      - Hartshorne, Hugh (Box V-1)
      - Hawkins, Peter (Box V-1)
      - Hays, Richard (Box V-1)
      - Hehir, J. Bryan (Box V-1)
      - Hein, Norvin (Box V-1)
      - Hicks, R. Lansing (Box V-1)
      - Hilton, Allen (Box V-1)
      - Holmer, Paul (Box V-1)
      - Huebner, Dwayne (Box V-1)
      - Jacks, L..P. (Box V-1)
      - Johnson, Robert (Box V-1)
      - Jones, Serene (Box V-1)
      - Kagawa, Toyohiko (Shaeffer Lecturer, 1931) (Box V-1)
      - Kavanagh, Aidan (Box V-1)
      - Keck, Leander (Box V-1)
      - Kelsey, David (Box V-1)
      - Kittel, Bonnie (Box V-1)
      - Kraeling, Carl H. (Box V-1)
      - Krigbaum, Charles (Box V-1)
      - Lara, Jaime (Box V-1)
      - Latourette, Kenneth Scott (Box V-1)
      - Leslie, Kristen (Box V-1)
      - Lindbeck, George (Box V-1)
      - Luccock, Halford E. (Box V-1)
      - Lull, David (Box V-1)
      - Lyke, Larry (Box V-1)
      - MacDougall, Detra (Registrar) (Box V-1)
      - McFague, Sallie (Box V-1)
      - Macintosh, Douglas Clyde (Box V-1)
      - Malherbe, Abraham (Box V-1)
      - Martin, Robert K. (Box V-1)
      - Miller, Francis P. (Box V-1)
      - Minear, Paul (Box V-1)
      - Morris, Raymond (Box V-1)
      - Muehl, E. William (Box V-1)
      - Murray, Thomas (Box V-1)
      - Napier, Davie (Box V-1)
      - Nelson, John O. (Box V-1)
      - Niebuhr, H. Richard (Box V-1)
      - Nouwen, Henri J. M. (Box V-1)
      - Noyce, Gaylord (Box V-1)
      - Ogletree, Thomas (Box V-1)
      - Outka, Gene (Box V-1)
      - Pelikan, Jaroslav (Box V-1)
      - Peterson, Stephen L. (Box V-1)
      - Pierson, George - Maintenance (Box V-1)
      - Pope, Marvin (Box V-1)
      - Porter, Frank (Box V-1)
      - Porter, Noah (Box V-1)
      - Rittgers, Ronald (Box V-1)
      - Rowthorn, Jeffery W. (Box V-1)
      - Russell, Letty (Box V-1)
      - Ruth, Lester (Box V-1)
      - Saliers, Donald (Box V-1)
      - Sandau, Wayne (Box V-1)
      - Sanneh, Lamin (Box V-1)
      - Schmidt, Benno Jr. (Box V-1)
      - Shedd, Clarence Prouty (Box V-1)
      - Smith, Robert Seneca (Box V-1)
      - Stevens, George B. (Box V-1)
      - Streets, Frederick J. (Box V-1)
      - Stroup, John (Box V-1)
      - Stubbs, Charles (Box V-1)
      - Stuehrenberg, Paul F. (Box V-1)
      - Swancutt, Diana (Box V-1)
      - Taylor, Nathaniel (Box V-1)
      - Towner, Sibley (Box V-1)
      - Turner, Philip (Box V-1)
      - Tweedy, Henry Hallam (Box V-1)
      - Uphaus, Willard (Box V-1)
      - Vieth, Paul H. (Box V-1)
      - Volf, Miroslav (Box V-1)
      - Watts, Leon
      - Weigle, Luther A. (see also OVERSIZE, framed)
      - West, Cornell
      - Williams, Colin
      - Wilson, Robert
      - Wood, Raymond
      - Woolsey, Theodore Dwight
      - OVERSIZE FACULTY PHOTOS
        - Bacon, Leonard (Box OV-3)
        - Day, George Edward
        - Fitch, Eleazar T.
        - Gibbs, Josiah W.
        - Goodrich, Chauncey A.
        - Taylor, Nathaniel W. (photo of bust)
        - Weigle, Luther
    - Staff
      - Blodgett, Barbara (Box V-1)
      - Bradshaw, Anita (Box V-1)
      - Brown, Martha (Box V-1)
      - Civitello, Louie- Maintenance Staff (Box V-1)
      - Ford, Robert (Box V-1)
      - Kathan, Boardman (Box V-1)
      - MacDougall, Detra (Box V-1)
      - Mullin, Frank (Box V-1)
      - Stebbins, Judy (Box V-1)
    - Buildings/Grounds
      - Construction and Dedication - 409 Prospect St. (Box V-2)
      - Gatherings and Services (Box V-2)
      - Institute of Sacred Music (Box V-2)
      - Marquand Chapel - Interior (Box V-2)
      - Marquand Chapel - Exterior (photography by Lisa Huck) (Box V-2)
      - Marquand Chapel scenes (Box V-2)
      - Harkness Memorial Quadrangle (Box V-2)
      - Old YDS Building (Box V-2)
      - Yale University and Campus, New Haven Scenes (Box V-2)
      - YDS Buildings - Exterior (Box V-2)
      - YDS Dormitories (Box V-2)
      - YDS Grounds (Box V-2)
      - YDS Refectory (Box V-2)
    - Students
      - Female Students, 1981 (Box V-2)
      - Student Activities- incl. theatrical performances, choral activities, 1930s-1950s, 1977-1978 (Box V-2)
      - Student activities, YDS basketball team, ca.1900s (Box V-2)
    - Class Photographs
      - Class of 1892
      - 1924 class photo
      - Class of 1934
      - Class of 1936
      - Class of 1937
      - Class of 1939
      - Class of 1947
      - Class of 1948
      - Class of 1915
      - Class of 1919
      - Class of 1924
      - Class of 1928-1929
      - Class of 1931
      - Class of 1932
      - Class of 1933
      - Class of 1934
      - Class of 1935
      - Class of 1936
      - Class of 1937
      - Class of 1938
      - Class of 1939
      - Class of 1940
      - Class of 1941
      - Class of 1942
      - Class of 1943
      - Class of 1944
      - Class of 1945
      - Class of 1946
      - Student body 1946-47
      - Class of 1947
      - Student body 1947-48
      - Class of 1948
      - Class of 1949
      - Class of 1950
      - 1950-51 student body (also entering students)
      - YDS School Picture 1950-1951
      - Class of 1951-1952
      - Entering students 1951-1954
      - Class of 1952-1953
      - Class of 1953-1954
      - Entering students 1955-1958
      - Class of 1959
      - Class of 1970
      - Class of 1972
      - Class of 1974
      - Class of 1976
      - Class of 1980
      - Class of 1982
      - Class of 1983
      - Class of 1984
      - Class of 1985
      - Class of 1986
      - Class of 1989
      - Class of 1991
      - Class of 2001
      - Class of 2002
      - Class of 2007
      - Class of 2009
      - Class of 2010
      - Class of 2011
      - Class of 2012
      - Class of 2013
      - Class of 2014
      - Class of 2015
    - Special Subjects
      - Basketball (Box V-2)
      - Berkeley Divinity School (Box V-2)
      - Classroom Scenes - miscellaneous (Box V-2)
      - Commencement Photographs - Dean Keck (Box V-3)
      - Convocation - 1982 (Box V-3)
      - Convocation - 1985 (Box V-3)
      - Convocation - 1987 (Box V-3)
      - Faculty Conference (Box V-3)
      - Parties - Christmas, 1984 (Box V-3)
      - Parties - Common Room receptions and gatherings (Box V-2)
      - Parties - At Dean Keck's house (Box V-2)
      - Parties - Reception in YDS Common Room (Box V-2)
      - Photographs of Events (Box V-2)
      - Visitors to YDS: Archbishop Robert Runcie (Box V-2)
      - Visitors to YDS: Madeleine L'Engle and husband (Box V-2)
      - YDS banner with seal (Box V-2)
      - Class of 1950 Reunion (Box V-2)
      - YDS Plays (Box V-2)
      - Misc. snapshots, including Quad renovation and dedication, Spring 2001; faculty group photos; first Divinity Library Renovation, 1950s. (Box V-6)
      - Miscellaneous - chronological, 1969-1990 (Box V-3)
      - Miscellaneous - chronological, 1991-1994 (Box V-4)
      - Miscellaneous - chronological, 1995-2018 (Box V-5)
    - Other media
      - Glass slides
        - Glass slides to accompany lectures on Palestine Archaeological Museum, Dead Sea Scrolls, Petra - The "Rose-Red City" of Transjordan (with text and cue cards)
      - Scrapbooks, 1922-1957
        - Scrapbook I - includes Articles and Clippings; Photos; Programs and Miscellaneous, 1922-1938
        - Scrapbook II - includes Articles and Clippings; Photos; Programs and Miscellaneous, 1937-1957
      - Posters
        - Tri-fold photo poster by Reid Huntley, Class of 1961: Scenes events of the course of his B.D. study, 1957-58, 1958-59, 1960-61
        - Tri-fold photo poster by Reid Huntley, Class of 1961: Scenes from 25th reunion; 30th reunion, 1986; 1992
        - Tri-fold photo poster by Reid Huntley, Class of 1961: Scenes from Cluster Reunion (for classes of 1961, 1962, 1963), 2007
      - Framed photos
        - Framed blue glass replica of YDS Shield, gift of Class of 1955
      - CD-ROM
        - Reunions 2004 (James R. Anderson Photography)
        - Commencement: Degree Ceremony, 2008
        - Summer Term, photos by Jennifer P. Sheridan, 2008 (Box V-6, Folder Misc.)
  - Audio
    - Named Lectures
      - Bainton Lectures
        - Matthews, Donald G: "One Nation Under God, Indivisable" (Tape), 1989 (Box 51A)
        - Washington, James: "The Crisis of Christian Conscience at the Nadir of the 20th Century" (Tape), 1990 (Box 51A)
        - Atkinson, Clarissa: "The Modesty of the Elephant: Marriage, Families and Holiness in the 16th Century" (Tape), 1991 (Box 51A)
        - Bellah, Robert: "Religious Pluralism and Religious Truth" (Tape), 1995 (Box 51A)
        - Miles, Margaret R: "Human Community and Responsibility: Living Beings and Rational Minds in Augustines Debate with Manicheans" (Tape), 1995 (Box 51A)
        - Raboteau, Albert: "In Search of Common Ground: Howard Thurman and Religious Community"(Tape), 1997 (Box 51A)
        - Turner, Frank M: "John Henry Newman, E.B. Pusey and the Commence of Religion in the Oxford Movement" (Tape), 1998 (Box 51A)
        - Newman, Barbara: "Seeing, Imagining, Believing: Adventures in Visionary Theology" (Tape), 2000 (Box 51A)
        - Sanneh, Lamin: "Antislavery for the Love of God: New Haven and the Campaign for Africa" (Tape), 2001 (Box 51A)
        - Midelfort, H.C. Erik, 2005 (Box 51A)
        - Van Engen, John: "Free Spirits, Harassed Regimes, and Arrogant Clerics: A New Look at Religious Communities in the Early 14th c. Low Countries", 2009 (Box 51A)
      - Bartlett Lectures
        - Stowe, David: "China and the Protestant Ethic" (Tape), 1989 (Box 51A)
        - Handy, Robert T: "The Plymouth Pilgrims' Progress: From Minor Colony to Major Saga" (CD/Tape), 1990 (Box 51A)
        - Woo, Franklin J: "China and New England: Lessions in Self and Society" (Tape), 1991 (Box 51A)
        - McGiffert, M: "Religion and Profit Do Jump Together: The 1st American Pilgrim" (Tape), 1992 (Box 51A)
        - Hatch, Nathan: "The Puzzle of American Methodism" (Tape), 1993 (Box 51A)
        - Noll, Mark: "The Theological Puzzle of the Civil War" (Tape), 1994 (Box 51A)
        - Cahill, Lisa Sowle: "The Family: A Christian Perspective" (Tape), 1995 (Box 51A)
        - Little, David: "Tolerating Intolerance: Some Reflections on Freedom of Religion as a Human Right" (Tape), 1995 (Box 51A)
        - Burt, Robert A: "Reconciling with Justice" (Tape), 1996 (Box 51A)
        - Koh, Harold Hongju: "How is International Human Rights Law Enforced?" (Tape), 1997 (Box 51A)
        - Townes, Emilie: "Growing Like Topsy" (Tape), 2000 (Box 51A)
      - Beecher Lectures, 1940-2013
        Lyman Beecher lectures on preaching founded at Yale Divinity School 1871. Audio files of The Lyman Beecher Lectures are available for purchase through the Divinity School's Student Book Supply: http://divinity.yale.edu/bookstore/sbs-convocation. An archival copy of each recording is listed in this series.
        - Auden, W.H.: "The Witness of Layman" (CD/Tape), 1949 (Box 52)
        - Wriston, Henry: " The Preacher as Teacher" (CD/Tape), 1949 (Box 52)
        - Luccock, Halford: "Communicating the Gospel" (5 CD/Tapes), 1953 (Box 52)
        - Dun, Augus (Audio Reel), 1956 (Box 53)
        - Niles, D.T.: "The Preachers Task and The Stone of Stumbling" (CD/Tape), 1957 (Box 53)
        - Kennedy, Gerald (4 Audio Reels), 1958 (Box 53)
        - Newbigin, Lesslie: "The Finality of Christ: 'The Clue to History'" (CD/Tape), 1966 (Box 52)
        - Read, David H.C.: "Sent From God" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1973 (Box 52)
        - Mitchell, Henry: "The Genius of the Black Pulpit" (5 CDs), 1974 (Box 54)
        - Napier, Davie: "Word of God, Word of Earth" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1975 (Box 54)
        - Taylor, Gardner: "How Shall They Preach?" (4 CDs/4 Tapes), 1976 (Box 54)
        - Buechner, Carl Frederic: "Telling the Truth; Gospel as Tragedy; Gospel as Comedy; Gospel as Fairy Tale" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1977 (Box 54)
        - Craddock, Fred: "Overhearing the Gospel: The Illusion of Truth without Imagination; The Illusion of Truth without Passion; A Modest Proposal: The Listener Overhears; A Modest Proposal: The Speaker is Overheard; A Discussion with Fred B. Craddock" (5 Tapes), 1978 (Box 54)
        - Claypool, John: "The Preaching Event: What? Why? How? When?" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1979 (Box 55)
        - Coffin, William Sloane: "Scared to Life: the Story of the Paralytic; David, Goliath, and the U.S.A.; The Arms Race and the Human Race; Some Thoughts For and About Ministers"(4 CDs/Tapes), 1980 (Box 55)
        - Ahlstrom, Sydney: "Origin: The Antinomian Crisis and the First American Revolution: Cotton; Founders of the Preacher-Theologian Tradition: Willard and J. Edwards; The Rise of Progressive Orthodoxy; From the New Divinity Men to the New Haven Heyday" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1981 (Box 55)
        - Trible, Phyllis: "Texts of Terror: Unpreached Stories" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1982 (Box 56)
        - Smith, Kelly Miller: "Social Crisis Preaching: Purview; Perception; Persepctive; Proclamation" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1983 (Box 56)
        - Stendahl, K: "The Art of Preaching" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1984 (Box 55)
        - Muehl, William: "The Preacher of Theologian" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1985 (Box 55)
        - Forbes, James: "The Anointing Makes the Difference in Preaching; The Difference in Concept and Content in Preaching; The Difference in Preparation and Process Preaching; The Spiritual Formation of Annointed Preachers" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1986 (Box 55)
        - Allen, Horace T: "The Lectionary - Hermeneutical Hope; The Lectionary - Pastoral Peril; At the Supper - Where is the Sermon?; At Baptism - What is Mystagogy?" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1987 (Box 55)
        - Coburn, John: "Grace, Prayer, Paradox, Vocation" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1988 (Box 55)
        - Brueggemann, Walter: "Finally Comes the Poet" [Lecture series title]. 1) "Numbness and Ache: The Strangeness of Healing"; 2) "Alienation and Rage: The Odd Invitation to Communion"; 3) "Restlessness and Greed: Obedience for Missional Imagination"; 4) "Power and Dream: A Permit to Freedom" (4 CDs/Tapes also available), 1989 (Box 55)
        - Proctor, Samuel D: "The Celebration of God's Presence and Participation in Human Affairs; The Assurance of Spiritual Renewal and Moral Wholeness; The Affirmation of Hope for Genuine Community; The Proclamation of the Eternal in the Midst of Time" (4 CDs/Tapes), 1990 (Box 55)
        - Bartlett, David: "Preaching on the Passion of Mark" (1 CD), 1991 (Box 56)
        - Malherbe, Abraham: "Paul: Pastor to Recent Converts" (1 CD), 1991 (Box 56)
        - Keck, Leander: "Toward the Renewal of Mainline Protestantism" (4 CD set), 1992 (Box 56)
        - Hoyt, Dr. Thomas Jr: "The Church's Preaching in Pluralistic and Ecumenical Context: Tradition; Particulariy: Let the Church Say Amen; Universality: What in the New World Disorder Shall They Preach?" (3 CD set), 1993 (Box 56)
        - Burghardt, Walter: "The Christian Pulpit and Social Justice" (2 CD set), 1994 (Box 56)
        - Adams, Harry Baker: "Preaching: The Burden and the Joy" (3 Tapes), 1995
        - Way, Peggy B: "Pastoral Epistemology: Method Metaphor Metatheology" (3 Tapes), 1995
        - Buttrick, David G: "The New and the Now: Speaking of God's New Order" (3 CD set), 1996 (Box 56)
        - Taylor, Barbara Brown: "Famine in the Land: Homiletical Restrait and the Silence of God" (3 CD set), 1997 (Box 56)
        - Gomes, Peter J: "The Texture of Biblical Preaching: Songs, Letters and Stories" (3 Tapes), 1998 (Box 56)
        - Lischer, Richard: "To What End? The Preaching for Reconciliation; One Last Story; The End of Words: Preaching the Gospel in a World Come of Age'The Ultimate Vocation'" (3 Tapes), 1999 (Box 56)
        - Lundblad, Barbara: "Marking Time: Stories Remembered at the River's Edge" (3 Tapes), 2000 (Box 56)
        - Bartlett, David L: "What's Good About This News" (3 Tapes), 2001 (Box 56)
        - Shephard, J. Barrie: "Poety, Parables and Preaching or Whatever Happened to Delight?" (on order), 2002 (Box 56)
        - Davis, Ellen: "The Art of Astonishing: Preaching From the Old Testament--The Presence of the Text; Maximal Speech: Preaching the Psalms; An Abundant Meaning" (3 Tapes), 2003 (Box 60b)
        - Moss, Otis Jr.: "Preaching as Prophetic Ministry--Personal: The Bold Adventure, Social Justice: The Tie that Binds, Global: The Binding Commitment" (CD), 2004 (Box 56)
        - Long, Thomas G.: "Preaching from Memory to Hope: 1. A Likely Story: The Perils and Power of Narrative in Preaching. -- 2. No News is Bad News: The Presence of the Word in Preaching. -- 3. Preaching in the Future Perfect Tense: Eschatology and Proclamation.", 2006 (Box 56)
        - Hawkins, Peter S.: "The Preacher's Divine Comedy--The Preacher in Hell" (CD), 2007 (Box 56)
        - Renita J. Weems Ph.D, Beecher Lectures 3 lectures (CD), 2008 (Box 56)
        - Eugene L. Lowry, Beecher Lectures, "Keeping Time with the Word: The Sound of the Sermon" 3 lectures (CD), 2009 (Box 56)
        - Mary Catherine Hilkert, Beecher Lectures, "Words of Spirit and Life" 3 lectures (CD), 2010 (Box 56)
        - Blount, Brian K.: I. "Dawn of the Dead: Preaching the Apocalypse"; II. "Apocalyptic Vulnerability: Preaching Paul"; III. "Invasion of the Dead: Preaching Mark." 3 lectures (CD), 2011 Oct 10-12 (Box 56)
        - Anna Carter Florence The Word in the Repertory Church Lecture I: The Script in the Scripture, the Word in Rehearsal: Proclamation in the Repertory Church Lecture II: "It Could Have Gone Differently": Repertory Readings of Texts of Terror Lecture III: Old Texts, New Works: The Repertory Preacher and the Company of Grace, 2012 Oct 24-26
        - Robin R. Meyers, "UNDONE: Faith as Resistance to Ego, Orthodoxy, and Empire" (Now available on Youtube: http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLbQINmUy3n7Yzm9pO4gO1BnZFAr14j5Ng), 2013 Oct 23-25
      - Cheney Lectures
        - Macquarrie, John: "Comitment" (2 Tapes), 1978 (Box 61)
        - Coggan, Donald: "Preparing for 21st Century Ministry and Mission" (3 Tapes), 1981 (Box 61)
        - O'Driscoll, Herbert: "The Apocalyptic Context of Contemp. Congregational Life" (2 Tapes), 1982 (Box 61)
        - Leech, Kenneth: "Prayer and Prophecy in the City: Some Reflections from the Urban British Scene" (2 Tapes), 1984 (Box 61)
        - Keating, Thomas: "The Clergy's Responsibility for Prayer (own/Parish)" (2 Tapes), 1986 (Box 61)
        - Mead, Loren: "Parishes: The Emerging Possibilities and Challenges" (Tape-Lecture 2 only), 1987 (Box 61)
        - Rothauge, Arlin: "The Modern Day Apostle in the Countryside" (Tape), 1988 (Box 61)
        - MacQuarrie, John: "Christology according to the Gospel of John" (2 Tapes), 1989 (Box 61)
        - Allison, The RT. Rev. C. Fitz Simmons: "The Pastoral Implications of Worship: What Happens to Our Self Rightousness, Fear, Hatred, Anger, and Hurt When we Worship?" (2 Tapes), 1990 (Box 61)